Guide to the Montana Attorney General's Office Records 1893-1969
Montana Historical Society Archives
- Subject Files
  - Annual and quarterly reports: State Colleges and Universities, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 26 / 60)
  - Annual and quarterly reports: state schools, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 26 / 61)
  - Annual reports: state agencies, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 27 / 1)
  - Annual reports: state institutions, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 27 / 2)
  - Annual reports: miscellaneous, 1941-1942 (Box-folder 27 / 3)
  - Armesworthey Estate, 1943 (Box-folder 27 / 4)
  - Bonds: Eastern Montana Normal School, 1941 (Box-folder 27 / 5)
  - Bonds: Montana State College, 1939-1941 (Box-folder 27 / 6)
  - Conference on State Defense, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 27 / 7-8)
  - Delinquent coal mines license taxes, 1925, 1938 (Box-folder 27 / 9-10)
  - Delinquent freight line taxes, 1938 (Box-folder 27 / 11)
  - Delinquent gasoline and distillate sales taxes, 1926-1927 (Box-folder 27 / 12)
  - Delinquent oil producers license taxes, 1926-1927, 1935-1937 (Box-folder 27 / 13-14)
  - Gambling investigation: Butte, 1942 (Box-folder 27 / 15)
  - Housing legislation, 1938 (Box-folder 27 / 16)
  - Interstate Commission on Crime, 1939 (Box-folder 27 / 17)
  - Liquor control, 1934-1936 (Box-folder 27 / 17a)
  - Montana Maternity Home and Hospital, 1942 (Box-folder 27 / 18)
  - Proposed legislation, 1939 (Box-folder 27 / 19)
  - Sheriff's mileage: Beaverhead County, 1937-1938 (Box-folder 27 / 20)
  - Utah Construction Company, 1941 (Box-folder 27 / 21)
  - Uniform Extradition Act, 1938 (Box-folder 27 / 22)
  - Works Progress Administration (WPA), 1936 (Box-folder 27 / 22a)
  - Denzil R. Young estate, 1942-1943 (Box-folder 27 / 23-24)
  - Accountants, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 1)
  - Admission to the Bar, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 2)
  - Adoption, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 3)
  - Agriculture, Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 4)
  - Aliens and Alien Property Custodian, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 5)
  - Anonymous, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 6)
  - Appointments, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 7)
  - Appropriations, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 8)
  - Attorneys General, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 9)
  - Aviation and aeronautics, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 10)
  - Bonds, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 11)
  - Cities and towns, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 12)
  - Citizens Incorporated, Butte, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 13)
  - Civil cases, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 14)
  - Complaints, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 15)
  - Contracts, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 16)
  - Corporations, 1948 (Box-folder 28 / 17)
  - Counties, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 18)
  - County Assessors, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 19)
  - County Attorneys: Beaverhead-Yellowstone, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 20-24)
  - County Attorneys: gambling reports, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 25)
  - County Clerks, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 26)
  - County Commissioners, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 27)
  - County Sheriffs, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 28)
  - County Superintendents of Schools, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 29)
  - County Treasurers, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 30)
  - Criminal cases, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 31)
  - Disbarment, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 32)
  - District courts and judges, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 33)
  - Doctors and hospitals, 1948 (Box-folder 28 / 34)
  - Elections, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 35)
  - Escheated estates, 1948 (Box-folder 28 / 36)
  - Estates, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 37)
  - Extradition, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 38)
  - Federal regulations, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 39)
  - Federal Works Agency, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 40)
  - Fees, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 41)
  - Firearms (re guns), 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 42)
  - Firemen, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 43)
  - Forestry, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 44)
  - Hospital Service Association (Blue Cross), 1948 (Box-folder 28 / 45)
  - Indians, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 46)
  - Insurance, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 47)
  - Irrigation and irrigation districts, 1947 (Box-folder 28 / 48)
  - Justices of the Peace, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 49)
  - Lands, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 50)
  - Laws and violations, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 28 / 51-54)
  - Leases and deeds, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 1)
  - Legislation and legislature, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 2)
  - Licenses, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 3)
  - Livestock, 1924-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 4)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 5)
  - Memoranda, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 6)
  - Military and military service, 1942, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 7)
  - Mines and mining, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 8)
  - Minors, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 9)
  - Miscellaneous, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 10)
  - Mitchell and Pershing, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 11)
  - Montana. Abstractors Board, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 12)
  - Montana. Aeronautics Commission, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 13)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1937, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 14)
  - Montana. Bank Examiner, 1948 (Box-folder 29 / 15)
  - Montana. Deaf and Blind School, 1948 (Box-folder 29 / 16)
  - Montana. Equalization Board, 1943-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 17)
  - Montana. Examiners, 1933, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 18)
  - Montana. Fish and Game Dept. (includes re Clifford Boyd land), 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 19-20)
  - Montana. Governor, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 21)
  - Montana. Health Board, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 22)
  - Montana. Highway Commission and Highway Patrol, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 23)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 24)
  - Montana. Insane, Hospital for the (Warm Springs), 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 25)
  - Montana. Land Commissioners, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 26)
  - Montana. Liquor Control Board, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 27)
  - Montana. Milk Control Board, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 28)
  - Montana. National Guard, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 29)
  - Montana. Northern Montana College, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 30)
  - Montana. Orphans' Home, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 31)
  - Montana. Prison, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 32)
  - Montana. Public Employees' Retirement Board, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 33)
  - Montana. Purchasing Agent, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 34)
  - Montana. Railroad Commission and Public Service Commission, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 35)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 36)
  - Montana. State College, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 37)
  - Montana. State University, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 38)
  - Montana. Superintendent of Public Instruction, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 39)
  - Montana. Supreme Court, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 40)
  - Montana. Teachers' Retirement System, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 41)
  - Montana. Trade Commission, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 42)
  - Montana. Tuberculosis Hospital, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 43)
  - Montana. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 44)
  - Montana. University System, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 45)
  - Montana. Water Conservation Board, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 46)
  - Mortgages and liens, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 47)
  - Naturalization, 1948 (Box-folder 29 / 48)
  - O'Donnell, Phil, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 29 / 49)
  - Official opinions, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 50)
  - Oil and gas matters, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 51)
  - Optometry, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 52)
  - Osteopathy, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 53)
  - Pardon and parole, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 54)
  - Pension, 1948 (Box-folder 29 / 55)
  - Personal, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 56)
  - Printing, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 57)
  - Proclamation, 1948 (Box-folder 29 / 58)
  - Property, real and personal, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 59)
  - Receipts, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 60)
  - Rent and rent control, 1947 (Box-folder 29 / 61)
  - Requests for information, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 62-65)
  - Requests for opinions, 1945-1948 (Box-folder 29 / 66-67)
  - Reports of Attorney General, 1944-1946 (Box-folder 30 / 1)
  - Roads and highways, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 2)
  - Salaries, 1947 (Box-folder 30 / 3)
  - Schools, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 4)
  - School transportation, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 5)
  - Social Security, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 6)
  - Surveyors, 1947 (Box-folder 30 / 7)
  - Tax deed lands, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 8)
  - Taxation, 1947 (Box-folder 30 / 9)
  - Teachers, 1947 (Box-folder 30 / 10)
  - Telegrams, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 11)
  - Unions and labor, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 12)
  - Vehicles, 1948 (Box-folder 30 / 13)
  - Veterans, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 14)
  - Welfare, 1947-1948 (Box-folder 30 / 15)
  - Wills, 1948 (Box-folder 30 / 16)
  - Young Democratic Club, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 30 / 17)
  - Abstracts and Abstractors Board, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 18)
  - Admissions to the Bar, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 19-20)
  - Adoption, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 21)
  - American Legion, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 30 / 22)
  - AMVETS, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 30 / 23)
  - Anonymous, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 24)
  - Appointments, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 25)
  - Appropriations, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 30 / 26)
  - Architecture, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 27)
  - Automobiles, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 30 / 28)
  - Banks, 1951 (Box-folder 30 / 29)
  - Bonds, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 30)
  - Bonus, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 31)
  - Budget, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 30 / 32)
  - Children, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 30 / 33)
  - Chiropractors, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 34)
  - Carey Land Act Board, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 30 / 35)
  - Civil Defense, 1951-1953 (Box-folder 30 / 36)
  - Civil Cases, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 37)
  - Claims, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 38)
  - Clerk of the Court, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 39)
  - Clerk of the Court, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 39)
  - Commendations, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 40)
  - Compensation, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 30 / 41)
  - Columbia Valley Administration, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 30 / 42)
  - Complaints, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 30 / 43-46)
  - Complaints, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 31 / 1-5)
  - Contests, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 31 / 6)
  - Contracts, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 31 / 7)
  - Corporations, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 31 / 8)
  - Zamri Cote Estate, 1951 (Box-folder 31 / 9)
  - Council of State Governments, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 31 / 10)
  - County Assessors, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 31 / 11)
  - County Attorneys: Beaverhead to Madison counties, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 31 / 12-23)
  - County Attorneys: Madison to Yellowstone counties, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 1-11)
  - County Clerks, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 32 / 12)
  - County Commissioners, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 13)
  - County Coroners, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 32 / 14)
  - County Superintendents of Schools, 1951 (Box-folder 32 / 15)
  - Criminal cases, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 16)
  - Dentistry, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 32 / 17)
  - "Dollars for Democrats", 1948 (Box-folder 32 / 18)
  - Easements, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 19)
  - Eight Hour Law, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 20)
  - Elections, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 21-22)
  - Employment, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 32 / 23)
  - Escheated estates, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 24-25)
  - Estates, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 32 / 26-27)
  - Extradition, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 1-2)
  - Fees, 1951 (Box-folder 33 / 3)
  - Fences, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 4)
  - Fire arms (re guns), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 5)
  - Fire departments, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 6)
  - Forestry, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 7)
  - Funds and apportionments, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 33 / 8)
  - Future Farmers of America (FFA), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 9)
  - Gambling, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 10-18)
  - Gambling: County Attorneys (Beaverhead-Sheridan counties), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 33 / 19-25)
  - Gambling: County Attorneys (Missoula-Yellowstone counties) (some out of order), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 1-5)
  - Gambling investigations: Helena, 1949 (Box-folder 34 / 6)
  - Gambling: publicity, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 34 / 7)
  - Gambling: miscellany, 1941-1950 (Box-folder 34 / 8-11)
  - Grain Testing Laboratory, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 12)
  - Grand Jury, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 13)
  - Grass conservation, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 14)
  - Hail insurance, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 15)
  - Charles E. Heisey Foundation, 1950 (Box-folder 34 / 16)
  - Hutterites, 1952-1956 (Box-folder 34 / 17)
  - Indians, 1947-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 18-20)
  - Insurance, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 21)
  - Interstate Commerce Commission hearing: Valier Community Club vs. Western Montana Railroad, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 34 / 22-23)
  - Investigations, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 34 / 24)
  - Invitations to speak, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 34 / 25-26)
  - Irrigation, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 34 / 27)
  - Justices of the Peace, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 34 / 28)
  - Lands, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 35 / 1-3)
  - Law (copies of), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 35 / 4-7)
  - Law enforcement, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 35 / 8-9)
  - Law violation, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 35 / 10)
  - Laws, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 35 / 11-14)
  - Leases, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 35 / 15)
  - Legislation and Legislature, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 35 / 16-17)
  - Licenses, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 35 / 18-19)
  - Liquor Control Act, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 35 / 20-21)
  - Liquor Control Act, 1952 (Box-folder 36 / 1)
  - Liquor investigation (includes transcript), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 2-7)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 8-10)
  - Military service, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 11)
  - Mines and mining, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 12)
  - Montana. Agriculture Dept., 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 13)
  - Montana. Agriculture Experiment Station, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 36 / 14)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 15)
  - Montana. Beauty and Barber boards, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 16-17)
  - Montana. Controller, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 18)
  - Montana. Dairy Commissioner, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 36 / 19)
  - Montana. Dental Examiners Board, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 36 / 20)
  - Montana. Eastern Montana College, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 36 / 21)
  - Montana. Education Board, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 36 / 22-25)
  - Montana. Education Board: Selection Committee, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 37 / 1)
  - Montana. Equalization Board, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 2)
  - Montana. Examiner, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 3)
  - Montana. Examiners, Board of, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 4-5)
  - Montana. Fish and Game Dept., 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 6-9)
  - Montana. Food Distributors, Board of, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 10)
  - Montana. Forester, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 37 / 11)
  - Montana. Governor, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 12)
  - Montana. Health, Board of, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 13)
  - Montana. Highway Commission, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 14-17)
  - Montana. Highway Patrol, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 18)
  - Montana. Historical Library, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 19)
  - Montana. Industrial Accident Board, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 20-21)
  - Montana. Industrial School for Boys (Reform School), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 37 / 22-23)
  - Montana. Lands Department, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 1-4)
  - Montana. Livestock Commission, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 5-6)
  - Montana. Medical Examiners Board, 1952 (Box-folder 38 / 7)
  - Montana. Milk Control Board, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 8)
  - Montana. Northern Montana College (includes dismissal of G.H. Vande Bogart), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 9-14)
  - Montana. Orphans' Home, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 38 / 15)
  - Montana. Prison, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 16)
  - Montana. Public Instruction, Dept. of, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 17)
  - Montana. Railroad Commission, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 18)
  - Montana. School for the Deaf and Blind, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 19)
  - Montana. School of Mines, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 20)
  - Montana. Secretary of State, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 21)
  - Montana. Soldiers' Home, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 38 / 22)
  - Montana. State College (Bozeman), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 38 / 23)
  - Montana. State Hospital (Warm Springs), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 38 / 24)
  - Montana. State Hospital (Warm Springs), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 1)
  - Montana. State Training School (Boulder), 1948-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 2)
  - Montana. State Tuberculosis Sanitarium (Galen), 1948-1951 (Box-folder 39 / 3)
  - Montana. State University (Missoula) (includes Stell Duncan Johnstone Fund), 1948-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 4-6)
  - Montana. Treasurer, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 7)
  - Montana. Unemployment Compensation Commission, 1946-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 8-10)
  - Montana. University Chancellor, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 11-12)
  - Montana. University System bond issues, 1946-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 13-16)
  - Montana. Vocational School for Girls (Mountain View), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 39 / 17)
  - Montana. Water Conservation Board, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 39 / 18)
  - Montana. Western Montana College (Dillon), 1948-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 19)
  - Montana Physicians Service, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 20-21)
  - Mortgage, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 22)
  - Nepotism, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 23)
  - News releases, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 24)
  - Nurses, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 39 / 25)
  - Oil and gas matters, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 40 / 1-2)
  - Old Age Home (Lewistown), 1949-1951 (Box-folder 40 / 3-4)
  - Organized crime, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 40 / 5)
  - Edwin G. Osness patent, 1952 (Box-folder 40 / 6)
  - Pardon and parole, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 40 / 7-8)
  - Pension, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 40 / 9)
  - Personal, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 40 / 10-17)
  - Photography, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 40 / 18)
  - Printing, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 40 / 19)
  - Prisoners, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 40 / 20)
  - Property, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 41 / 1)
  - Proposed legislation, 1948-1951 (Box-folder 41 / 2)
  - Public Employees Retirement System, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 41 / 3-4)
  - Punchboards (gambling), 1951-1952 (Box-folder 41 / 5)
  - Requests for opinion, 1949-1951 (Box-folder 41 / 6-21)
  - Requests for opinion, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 42 / 1-14)
  - Retirement systems, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 42 / 15)
  - Roads, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 42 / 16)
  - Charles M. Russell Memorial Commission, 1951 (Box-folder 42 / 17)
  - Salaries, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 42 / 18)
  - Salvation Army, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 42 / 19)
  - School Transportation, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 42 / 20)
  - Schools, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 42 / 21-23)
  - Sheriffs, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 1)
  - Slot machines (gambling, includes report), 1949-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 2-3)
  - Soil conservation, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 4)
  - Special investigations, 1949 (Box-folder 43 / 5)
  - Stocks and bonds, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 6)
  - Albert Lee Stuart Estate, 1950-1951 (Box-folder 43 / 7)
  - Subversive activities (re communists), 1951-1956 (Box-folder 43 / 8)
  - Taxation, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 9-12)
  - Taylor Grazing Fund, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 43 / 13)
  - Teachers Retirement System, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 14-15)
  - Tschirgi Lease, 1949 (Box-folder 43 / 16)
  - Unfair Practice Law, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 17)
  - Vacation Law, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 18-19)
  - Veterans, 1948-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 20)
  - Veterans and Pioneers Building (Montana Historical Society building), 1951-1954 (Box-folder 43 / 21)
  - Veterans Bonus, 1950-1952 (Box-folder 43 / 22-25)
  - Veterans of Foreign Wars (VFW), 1949-1950 (Box-folder 43 / 26)
  - Vocational Rehabilitation, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 43 / 27)
  - Warm Springs Store and Hotel, 1949-1950 (Box-folder 44 / 1)
  - Water matters, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 44 / 2-3)
  - Welfare, 1949-1952 (Box-folder 44 / 4-8)
  - "Old correspondence: save for reference", 1951-1952 (Box-folder 44 / 9)
  - Admission to the Bar, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 10)
  - Adoption, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 11)
  - Appointments, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 12)
  - Appropriations, 1953 (Box-folder 44 / 13)
  - Architecture, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 14)
  - Athletic Committee, 1953 (Box-folder 44 / 15)
  - Attorneys General, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 16)
  - Automobiles, 1954 (Box-folder 44 / 17)
  - Banks and banking, 1953 (Box-folder 44 / 18)
  - Bonds, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 19)
  - Children, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 20)
  - Chiropractors, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 21)
  - Claims, 1950-1956 (Box-folder 44 / 22)
  - Complaints, 1953-1955 (Box-folder 44 / 23-25)
  - Contracts, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 26)
  - Copy of law, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 27)
  - Corporations, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 28)
  - County Assessor, 1954 (Box-folder 44 / 29)
  - County Attorneys: Beaverhead-Custer, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 44 / 30-33)
  - County Attorneys: Daniels-Yellowstone, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 1-14)
  - County Auditors, 1954 (Box-folder 45 / 15)
  - County Clerks, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 16)
  - County Commissioners, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 17)
  - County Sheriffs, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 18)
  - Criminal cases, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 19)
  - Dentistry, 1953 (Box-folder 45 / 20)
  - Doctors and hospitals, 1954 (Box-folder 45 / 21)
  - Elections, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 22)
  - Employment, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 23)
  - Escheated estates, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 24)
  - Estates, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 25)
  - Extradition, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 26)
  - Federal regulations, 1953 (Box-folder 45 / 27)
  - Firearms (re guns), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 28)
  - Fire departments and laws, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 29)
  - Form letters, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 30)
  - Future Farmers of America (FFA), 1953 (Box-folder 45 / 31)
  - Gambling: legalized, 1954 (Box-folder 45 / 32)
  - Gambling: Beaverhead-Yellowstone counties, 1950-1954 (Box-folder 45 / 33-46)
  - Gambling: miscellaneous, 1949-1955 (Box-folder 46 / 1)
  - Indians: jurisdiction, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 2-3)
  - Indians: proposed dissolution of Flathead Reservation, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 4)
  - Indian Affairs Institute, 1954 (Box-folder 46 / 5)
  - Insurance, 1954 (Box-folder 46 / 6)
  - Investigations: Goose Bay State Park (Barney Rankin), 1953-1956 (Box-folder 46 / 7)
  - Investigations: prostitution, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 8)
  - Irrigation, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 9)
  - Justices of the Peace, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 10)
  - Lands, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 11)
  - Laws and law violations, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 12)
  - Leases, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 13)
  - Licenses, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 14)
  - Marriage and divorce, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 15)
  - Medical insurance (correspondence and reports), 1951-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 16-17)
  - Military service, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 18)
  - Mines and mining, 1954 (Box-folder 46 / 19)
  - Miscellaneous, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 20)
  - Montana. Adjutant General, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 21)
  - Montana. Agriculture Dept., 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 22)
  - Montana. Auditor, 1954-1955 (Box-folder 46 / 23)
  - Montana. Beauty and Barber Boards, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 24)
  - Montana. Carey Land Act Board, 1953 (Box-folder 46 / 25)
  - Montana. Controller, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 26)
  - Montana. Eastern Montana College of Education, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 27)
  - Montana. Education, Board of, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 28)
  - Montana. Engineer, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 29)
  - Montana. Equalization, Board of, 1951-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 30)
  - Montana. Examiner, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 46 / 31)
  - Montana. Fish and Game Department, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 1)
  - Montana. Forestry Board, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 2)
  - Montana. Governor, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 3)
  - Montana. Health, Board of, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 4)
  - Montana. Highway Dept., 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 5)
  - Montana. Highway Patrol, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 6)
  - Montana. Historical Society, 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 7)
  - Montana. Home for Senile Aged (Lewistown), 1953-1954 (Box-folder 47 / 8)